

ADAYEHI JONATHAN

PROFILE

Well-organized, creative, and proven software engineer and website developer. Experience working with and across development teams as well as external clients on creative, technical, strategic, and tactical levels. Significant experience in coding and debugging. Track record of delivering unique and effective software solutions. Impressive history of designing and launching highperformance websites and applications.

CONTACT

PHONE:

(234+) 8105614442

LINKEDIN:

www.linkedin.com

EMAIL

jonathanKingoche@gmail.com

✓ BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN GEOGRAPHY AND PLANNING

UNIVERSITY OF JOS 2017 - 2023

HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP JAVASCIPT, REACT PHP, PYTHON 70% HARD WORD, TEAM WORK, CREATIVITY, COMMUNICATION AND MORE

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER & WEB DEVELOPER ALX SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROGRAM

April 2022–June 2023 Engaged in challenging projects in coding, website development, and mobile app creation, gaining extensive experience in various programming languages including C, C++, Python, HTML, CSS, Ruby, and PHP. Developed client-specific websites and apps, and conducted coding classes.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER & INSTRUCTOR FREELANCER VARIOUS LOCATION

SEPTEMBER 2022–DATE Managed the development of high-quality websites for educational institutions. Teaching coding classes, mentoring students in modern techniques. Developed mobile apps example, computer base examination platform and a sophisticated to-do list application. Integrated cutting-edge technologies into teaching content, promoting continuous learning and innovation.

EDUCATION

- ✓ BACKEND WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT ALX SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROGRAM 2022 – 2023
- ✓ FRONTEND WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT META 2023 – 2024
- ✓ CYBERSECURITY

GOOGLE IN PROGRE